<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Open Graph | Carrot Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.gocarrot.com/blog/categories/open-graph/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.gocarrot.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-04T14:16:01-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.gocarrot.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Carrot Inc.]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Carrot]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.gocarrot.com/blog/2012/12/03/introducing-carrot/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-03T16:20:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.gocarrot.com/blog/2012/12/03/introducing-carrot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to Carrot.</p>

<p>Carrot provides your application with the best tools in the industry for viral distribution on the world's largest social graph. We offer a robust server solution combined with lightweight, easy to use SDKs to get you up and running quickly and reliably, and a drag-and-drop visual editor for your virals with metrics integration so you can monitor, tune and increase the distribution of your app.</p>

<p><img class="thumbnail" src="http://gocarrot.com/assets/image/high-scores/png"></p>

<p>With Carrot your app's achievements, scores and user actions become viral powerhouses that draw in new users and re-engage existing users. We provide automated tournaments with viral actions sent to the winners which will keep your users coming back each week.</p>

<p>Carrot is virals done <strong>right</strong>.</p>

<!-- More -->


<h2>Open Graph</h2>

<p>Carrot hands you the reins for <a href="https://developers.facebook.com/docs/concepts/opengraph/">Open Graph</a>, Facebook's API that allows rich integration into their social graph. Our cloud-based server stack was built to handle the firehose, navigate the changing Facebook regulations and distil it down to an easy-to-use set of visual editors and constant SDK so you can focus on making your app <em>great</em>.
<img src="http://gocarrot.com/assets/image/docs-achievement-en/png">
Forget building a backend, complicated Facebook requests, the constantly changing Graph API, and updating XML tags; Carrot lets developers focus on the application, and gives growth managers a full-featured toolset for updating and optimizing viral features.</p>

<h2>Metrics, Metrics, Metrics!</h2>

<p>Who likes metrics? We like metrics! Carrot tracks and records clicks, exit-paths, link referrals, browser stats, and integrates them with your app's Facebook Insights to give you the data you need to maximize the viral growth of your application.
<img src="http://gocarrot.com/assets/image/metrics/png"></p>

<h2>Mobile Friendly</h2>

<p>Carrot was designed with mobile in mind. Our mobile SDKs cache user actions on the device to make sure they are never lost. We offer the easiest to use Facebook Single-Sign-On wrapper to let you get your users authenticated and back to using your app quickly and seamlessly.</p>

<h3>Carrot + Unity = Cake</h3>

<p><img class="pull-right" src="http://gocarrot.com/assets/image/unity128/png" width="100" height="100">
There's no two ways about it: Carrot loves Unity. Our editor extensions make using Carrot with Unity a breeze. Enter your app's Carrot credentials in our UI window and you are good to go. Our post build scripts will make sure Xcode's plist files contain all the needed Facebook information, and automatically makes the needed modifications to the Unity-generated source code.</p>

<h3>Carrot and Game Center: Best Friends Forever</h3>

<p><img class="pull-right" src="http://gocarrot.com/assets/image/gamecenter500/png" width="100" height="100">
If your app has Game Center achievements there's no need to re-enter the information in Carrot, we'll pull in descriptions, points, images and translations with the click of a button. Your Game Center achievements will transform from a 'pat on the back' for your users into viral growth for your application.</p>

<h2>When? How Much?</h2>

<p>We'll be moving into open beta before the holidays with our free tier. You'll get achievements, scores and the ability for users to 'Like' your app without switching out to a web view.</p>

<p>Our paying tiers will include custom Open Graph objects and actions, automated tournaments, and the ability to create Open Graph objects on-the-fly. These features will be available to closed beta customers and we'll be rolling them out early next year to the world at large.</p>

<p>We are committed to making Carrot the best toolset for viral distribution that the industry has ever seen. We can't wait to show you what's in store for Carrot.</p>

<h2>I Can't Wait That Long!</h2>

<p>Well then we have good news for you: Our free tier is in closed beta right now! Send us an e-mail: <a href="mailto:beta@gocarrot.com">beta@gocarrot.com</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
